<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hattie, being on hattie, today</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hattie, being on hattie, today</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>September Incident Reports</title>
      <link>/seasons/september/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/seasons/september/</guid>
      <description>September 18th, 2021 i&#39;d prefer to meet the sun before it meets me first and
i&#39;d like to stand beneath it, warm summer-like and coolly say:
so imagine we&#39;re you-and-i-whispering to each other about
something or other, maybe god, but at least devout luckiness
i&#39;d prefer not to care how i write my poetry
it&#39;s like i&#39;m talking myself into a flow state immersive
o, pour from my pen / no my type /</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumnal Processional</title>
      <link>/seasons/poetry-on-autumn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/seasons/poetry-on-autumn/</guid>
      <description>Freytag&amp;rsquo;s Plot Pyramid Without the Climax &amp;amp; Especially With It all who make love tonight are good poets
but what of all 17 syllables i birthed with formal announcement
to you, holiest, only to offer another&#39;s iambic offspring as
my sacred sacrifice for the sake of
letting you think i am more inspired
than i am prolific than i am pregnable
pregnant with a prayer that
my third grade kiss satisfies</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holidays, Grasping</title>
      <link>/seasons/winter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/seasons/winter/</guid>
      <description>Lies I Tell About Cancer Today, I lied about picking my mother up from chemo
but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t lying about the chemo, my mom is dying,
and so I have the right to lie
(down in surrender, but please never let me)
My name is Hattie and I tell lies about cancer and I am afraid of driving because of crashing then dying but I tell others and myself that is not so&amp;ndash; I say that my mother told me I was afraid, and so I was, and so I am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Dilapidation</title>
      <link>/seasons/late-winter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/seasons/late-winter/</guid>
      <description>I Lie About Cancer and I’ll Keep Fucking Going i&amp;rsquo;m so volatile
that my concrete tragedy
is easier for you to digest
than the tumorous nothing
that i’m growing in my hands
that the oncologist thinks it moved into the brain
i&amp;rsquo;m so dramatic
but if i don&amp;rsquo;t give pain as performance
it could never be sensational art.
i’d be left at the mercy of your empathy, and
for your consideration:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letters from Spring</title>
      <link>/seasons/early-spring/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/seasons/early-spring/</guid>
      <description>Depression, Today, Feels Like a Homecoming. I write you to confess that I&amp;rsquo;m scared.
I don’t know where it stops or starts,
but I’m driving, and I’m in my way.
I write you to say I know nothing as ever.
I write poetry about my ascension before I can even begin.
It adds more distance. I go deeper.
I write from something somehow lower.
I am wrecked and begging.
I am abandoned and I tolerate no noise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer in Grace</title>
      <link>/seasons/summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/seasons/summer/</guid>
      <description>Event Log at the Escapist Palace We sit on the precipice.
Behind us the earth pushes forward—slowly, carefully,
only when we aren&amp;rsquo;t looking.
On my back is a vortex, and the whole world enters in pairs.
Two turkeys, two doe, two bucks, two babies,
and the two of us, bewildered and searching.
God lives in the ground here, and each of us knows this is true.
We kiss it with whatever our mouth looks like today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The revolution will be complete when the language is perfect</title>
      <link>/posts/language-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/language-perfect/</guid>
      <description>He moved over to the window Since about that time, war had been literally continuous, though strictly speaking it had not always been the same war. For several months during his childhood there had been confused street fighting in London itself, some of which he remembered vividly.
Inside the flat a fruity voice was reading out a list of figures which had something to do with the production of pig iron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On an unsung name</title>
      <link>/posts/sanity-not-statistical/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sanity-not-statistical/</guid>
      <description>i am rebirth of new seasons i am pitcherfull of sweet i am an unmelting snowflake
that may thursday meet
mister hide out
and at it again
pretending he likes me
in front of his friends
fine tuned possession
lives one day at a time
for my silent lysistrata
my unannounced rhyme</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I surprise you in a Lowe&#39;s</title>
      <link>/posts/destruction-of-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/destruction-of-words/</guid>
      <description>the way you draw a face
passed down unto
mine: drawn like a graph not passed down, i should
clean and fold and check my
bank account daily, i&amp;rsquo;m again
overdrawn or drowning. yes
terday i asked for your help
slowing down. today i found you
mourning in a lowes, we hold each
other in an instance: a joke about fruit flies from a false kitchen we do not recognize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Happiness is holding a flower in each hand. Hattie Sager is comprised of springtime peonies and late summer&amp;rsquo;s dahlias. She can be found walking to grocery stories, pushing her shoulders back, engaging in martyrdom, and being loved in return.
When asked to sing, she cries. When asked to cry, she holds. When asked to hold, she runs. When asked to run, she walks. When asked to walk, she always says yes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
